ari-soft.com 2009-06-26

# ARI Soft - Privacy Policy

You currently have **0 items** in your cart.

  * 27/05/2009 ARI Smart Content plugins repository

We are glad to announce that the new version of ARI Smart Content 1.7.0 is ready. Some bugs have been fixed in this version. Besides it allows working with plugins from [ARI Smart Content plugins repository](http://smart.ari-soft.com/component/option,com_phocadownload/Itemid,15/view,sections/ "Plugins repository"). Repository contains plugins that can widen the component's functionality. Now it contains only several plugins but their number will be increased constantly. You don't need to pay to get acccess to repository, everyone who has ARI Smart Content (DataTable Pack, Image Pack, News Pack) will be able to use these plugins.

  * 07/05/2009 ARI Smart Content 1.6.0 is available

We are glad to inform you of ARI Smart Content 1.6, ARI Smart Content: Image Pack 1.6, ARI Smart Content: DataTable Pack 1.6 and ARI Smart Content: News Pack 1.6 release. Process of installation is improved in the new version. Besides, a new 'Diagnostics' page is added in order to analyze and get rid of problems with a component. More over, new plugin  ARI JTruncator is added to ARI Smart Content and ARI Smart Content: News Pack. This plugin provides simple yet customizable truncation for text entities in your web page, also ARI JDialog plugin was improved and contains new features. You can view the components in action on our [demo site](http://smart.ari-soft.com/ "ARI Smart Content demo site") .

ARI Soft Privacy Policy is deeply committed to protecting the privacy of our customers.

We do not track, collect or distribute personal information about visitors of our website. The only information we track is about the visits to our web sites: we compile statistics that show the daily number of visitors to our sites, the daily requests we receive for particular files on our web sites, and what countries those requests come from. This information is used to help us make our services better and the statistics contain no personal information and cannot be used to gather such information.

If you decide to register on our website and forum your personal information required by register process will be added to our user database. If you would like to remove your information from our user database we will delete all your personal data.

Your personal information will not be released to third parties and shared among other users except to further the purpose for which you had provided the information, such as making specific requests for information, or if you request that your email be forwarded. There are no other circumstances under which we will provide or sell personal information to third parties.
